

JuanE.do Cubillo Carranza

Customer Service and Electronic Technician

PROFILE

Works with virtual and global teams, creating best practices. Exhibits all the best traits of Intel Contingent and ex-amazon employ with a "Research and develop" attitude, analytical approach, to get the job done while using diplomacy, being polite, calm, friendly, fostering teamwork, inclusion, and embracing servant leadership. Works well under pressure, known for great teaming, Microsoft Office Suite, communication skills, customer service, process improvement, responsibility, data analysis, proven excellent writing skills, analytical and problem-solving skills.

CONTACT

PHONE: 506-6161-0518

EMAIL:

juanedoc@hotmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native English Advance

REFERENCES

Carlos Cascante Montero-PM
 P: 7121-2688(whatsapp only)
 Adriana Avillan HRBP
 P:6436-0092

EDUCATION

ULATINA: Business Administration, IT and Electronics Engineering
Studies in progress - 2019
COVAO (Colegio Vocacional de Artes Y Oficios): Vocational degree
New Horizons: Advanced Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point, Access)

WORK EXPERIENCE

INFOTREE GLOBALSERVICES:

May 2019 – March 2023 (INTEL as CW)
Team leader assembly, Test and finish
Troubleshooting service support for Eng
Process Specialist manufacturing AT Intel

AMAZON INC:

October 2016 – March 2019 Customer Service Specialist Escalation Leadership Onboarding Process Specialist

COASIN Company

October 2020– now (partime Electronic devices repair and IQ Technical Support and R&D for telecomucation companies LAB

Longtech S.A

January 2010 - March 2014

Team leader and Ops Manager Assistant
Electronic R&D for Electronic devices IQ

- Excellent written, verbal communication and interpersonal relationships
 - Advance Excel skills and Teaching skills on Advanced Formulas, Tables, and Formatting, Advanced Charting, Pivot Tables and Pivot Reporting, Macros, VLOOKUP, Conditional Formatting
 - Customer Service skills and Time Management skills with conflict resolution for better customer experience
 - People management and problem-solving negotiate, resolve conflicts and lead in influencing decision making
 - Strategic Prospecting skills, multi-tasking
 - Managing Risks, Leadership, Agile and Design Thinking skills
 - Support general contract management through asset management, audit readiness, financial process support, issues management, measurements reporting, project plan execution, and, where applicable, request for service
 - Soft skills at work also using the STAR method to solve any issues
 - Sales skills using data mining and requirements based on the customer needs
 - Lead labs department to research and develop recovery for several spare parts, as a leader with the technician expertise to develop best-known practices to rework and fix, update the firmware and hardware improve to get performance with a high level of SLA's for international brands
 - Headship at intel labs department to develop also the best troubleshooting manual for new hires to get a soft process for the company at any time.
 - GEMBA and KAIZEN event for process improvement
 - RED CROSS and SCOUT volunteer in my free time help to improve our community and giving guidance to our young boys as a scout, as Red Cross help to other, first AID and ERT approach when is required